Anita Das

Specialist-Package Implementation

Phone: +91-8971093444

Email ID: anitadas.abap@gmail.com



OBJECTIVE

Seeking a challenging career in ERP as SAP ABAP consultant Professional where I can contribute my skills and knowledge for the growth of organization and to be able to implement the solution that meets the customer requirement.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

• Overall, 8 years of experience as ABAP Developer

TECHNICAL SKILLS

ERP : SAP R/3 in ECC 6.0, ECC 7.4

Programming

Language : SAP ABAP, C, C++

Office Tools : MS Office, Excel Word, Power Point

Operating System : Windows XP Professional, Windows 7, Windows 10

SAP Domains : SAP SD, SAP MM, SAP Fi/CO

ABAP SKILLS

Reporting : Classical, Interactive, ALV Report, OOABAP Report

Enhancements : Customer Exits, Badi and Enhancements

Interfaces : Bapi, ALE/IDOC

Data Conversion : LSMW, BDC-Session and Call Transaction Methods

Forms : Sap Scripts, Smart Forms SAP Hana : CDS View, AMDP, Odata

Tools : Debugger, Run time Analyzer, SQL Trace, SLT

TRAINING

Internal trainings on SAP ABAP on HANA.

Internal trainings on Odata.

CERTIFICATION

SAP Certified Development Specialist - ABAP for SAP HANA 2.0

WORK EXPERIENCE

Working as SAP ABAP Consultant in LTIMINDTREE Pvt Ltd. From (January 2020 to till date).

Client : Procter & Gamble

Client Profile: The Procter & Gamble Company (P&G) is an American multinational consumer goods corporation headquartered in Cincinnati, Ohio, founded in 1837 by William Procter and James Gamble. It specializes in a wide range of personal health/consumer health, and personal care and hygiene products; these products are organized into several segments including Beauty; Grooming; Health Care; Fabric & Home Care; and Baby, Feminine, & Family Care.

Roles & Responsibilities:

SAP FI/SD/MM:

- Requirement discussions with the functional consultants.
- Propose Better Business solutions both functionally and technically.
- Preparation of Technical Approach, Technical Document and Unit Test Report.
- Code review for new developments.
- Worked on configuration of UDM Dispute cases in S/4 system.
- Worked on Lockbox enhancements using Customer Exits.
- Worked on Aging report to display open items and the calculation for each line item based on date and customer provided by the user.
- Extensively worked on performance improvements of Aging report.
- Worked on SMARTFORMS for FI (Delivery Challan and Payment Voucher)
- Worked on Conversion report during go-live data upload.
- Worked on Inbound Idoc implementation from scratch.
- Developed Reconciliation and Ancillary Billing report.
- Developed interactive report for GRC module.
- Extensively working on SLT tool to replicate data from ECC to S4 HANA system.
- ❖ Worked as ERP Analyst in NTT Data from June 2016 to Dec 2019.

Client : Mercedes-Benz India Pvt Ltd - Daimler

Client Profile : Mercedes-Benz is a global automobile manufacturer and a division of the German company Daimler AG. The brand is known for luxury vehicles, buses, coaches, and trucks. The headquarters of Mercedes-Benz are in Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg, Germany.

Roles & Responsibilities:

SAP FI/SD/MM:

- Requirement discussions with the functional consultants.
- Preparation of Technical Approach, Technical Document and Unit Test Report.
- Migration of SAP BI_DWH Interfaces (26 Reports) from ECC to S4 system and Code optimization.
- Enhancement of ME21N While creating PO for a particular document type (small buy) and if amount range in between 50k to 80k a FORM will generate and send

mail to the Vendor and PR creator's email.

- Asset Annual Investment Report.
- Developed 26 classic reports for SAP BI DWH Interfaces.
- Developed a form, which lists the customer open items and provides a beginning balance and closing balance for a given period.
- Extensively worked on Code optimization.
- Worked as SAP ABAP Consultant in IBM from June 2014 to Feb 2016.

Client : Honda Europe, UK

Client Profile: Honda Motor Company, Ltd is a Japanese public multinational conglomerate manufacturer of automobiles, motorcycles, and power equipment, headquartered in Minato, Tokyo, Japan.

Roles & Responsibilities:

- Support and maintenance
- Analysis of functional documents and preparations of technical specifications.
- Documentation of unit test cases.
- Change Requests, Enhancements, Bug fixing.
- Extracted a report of Sales Orders in Status 'B' and 'C' for one-month duration from current date for HMEUK Motorcycles.
- Developed an aging report for motorcycles, which displays the number of days the vehicle in stock.
- Enhanced Sales order to round final price to the nearest whole number when using custom mark-ups and for custom pricing condition using BADI.
- Extended standard IDoc CREMAS05 to ZCREMAS05 to add with the new fields. So
 that the interface is to replicate the entire Vendor's and Inter Company Vendors
 created, changed, Blocked/Unblocked, flagged for deletion and Mass changes.

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Always believed in Commitment towards work.
- Possess Positive Attitude towards everything.
- Ability to adapt well to situations and technologies.
- Quick learner and always eager to learn new things.
- Have always met the deadlines and been a trustworthy resource for my lead.

• EDUCATIONAL SUMMARY

• Master's degree : MCA from Sambalpur University, Odisha

Graduation degree : BSc. From Utkal University, Odisha

PERSONAL PROFILE

Name Anita DasGender FemalePlace Bangalore